epaperflip.com 2014-09-22

# Privacy Policy | ePaperFlip

DCatalog, Inc. is doing business as ePaperFlip, hereinafter referred to as ePaperFlip. ePaperFlip service and related services, applications, domains and networks offered by ePaperFlip (“ePaperFlip service”). The ePaperFlip service allows you to connect, collaborate, share, and remix documents with other users of the ePaperFlip service community on the Internet. ePaperFlip’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using the ePaperFlip service. By using or accessing the ePaperFlip service, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy

### Information Gathered by ePaperFlip:

For visitors to our website and registered users, we log standard technical information, such as your IP address. If you choose to register with us, ePaperFlip requires you to provide your name, email address, and each user has a user ID and password that they choose. To maintain privacy it is important not to share your password with anyone. Selecting a longer password with a mix of letters, numbers and symbols makes it more difficult for others to guess your password. It is also helpful to change passwords on a regular basis. In addition, ePaperFlip will require you to provide geographical information such as your physical address. In the future ePaperFlip may ask you to provide other demographic information, such as age, gender, interests or occupation, as well as credit card information for verification purposes.

We may collect other personal information when you provide feedback or comments, or communicate with others through our systems. ePaperFlip also uses “cookies” – small files containing a string of characters sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser – in addition to Flash shared browser objects to administer its website and provide a more tailored and user-friendly service to you. For example, we may use cookies or Flash objects to count the number of unique computers accessing our website. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from the ePaperFlip service if you choose. When you access the ePaperFlip service or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This “automatically collected” information may include IP Address, a unique device or user ID, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the ePaperFlip service, and the dates and times that you visit the ePaperFlip service.

### ePaperFlip Uses of Information: 

The information we collect about you in the course of our relationship is used to provide the ePaperFlip service to you. For example, as we endeavor to protect your identity, we may use your demographic information to create a database of user profiles, select advertisements based on your information and for marketing analysis. In addition, we look at technical information to diagnose problems with our systems, to administer the ePaperFlip service, and to enhance the services we provide to you. We may use your information to track user-generated content and users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the ePaperFlip service.

ePaperFlip uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our users, to improve the way the ePaperFlip service works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. ePaperFlip may use “automatically collected” information, “cookies”, and Flash objects to: (a) automatically update the ePaperFlip service; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the ePaperFlip service; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, participation and status in any promotions or other activities, and usage of the ePaperFlip service.

### When ePaperFlip Discloses Information:

ePaperFlip does not share your personally identifiable information, including any of your user profile data that you create, with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses. Please be aware, however, that 1) any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on the ePaperFlip service becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction; and 2) as a feature of the ePaperFlip service, other users may become aware of your behavior or document viewing activities to their own profile pages and may use this information without restriction; provided that you will have the ability to opt out of this feature at anytime. ePaperFlip may share personally identifiable information about our users with third parties, including: (a) with your consent or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy; (b) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order; (c) where required by law; or (d) at our sole discretion, where we deem necessary to respond to claims, to protect the safety of any individual or the public, or to protect the rights or property of the ePaperFlip service or any third party. We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated companies, sub-contractors, other agents or businesses or persons to: provide website hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist ePaperFlip in improving the ePaperFlip service and creating new service features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures to keep your information secure. ePaperFlip may also disclose to third parties anonymous aggregated user information that is not personally identifiable. 

### Changing or Deleting Your Information:

You have the ability and control to remove or alter your account-specific information, including any user profile data that you provide to the ePaperFlip service at any time. Access and control over most user-provided personal information on the ePaperFlip service is readily available through the edit function on your profile. As a user of the ePaperFlip service, you may modify or remove any of your profile information at any time by logging into your account. Information will be updated promptly. If you wish to deactivate your ePaperFlip service account, you may do so. Removed information such as your user ID, geographical information connected to your user ID, and any documents that you have uploaded to the ePaperFlip service may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time, and thus may continue to be publicly available across features of the ePaperFlip service such as its search engine, but will not be generally accessible by ePaperFlip or users of the ePaperFlip service.

### Data Security:

ePaperFlip will take appropriate security measures designed to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. ePaperFlip processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. ePaperFlip takes reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

We endeavor to restrict access to personal information to ePaperFlip employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and are required to meet these obligations.

If ePaperFlip learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. ePaperFlip may post a notice on the ePaperFlip service if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at privacy@ePaperFlip.com.

### Children Under 13:

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE ePaperFlip SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.

ePaperFlip complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13, or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on the ePaperFlip service. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a member of the ePaperFlip service, then please contact ePaperFlip at privacy@ePaperFlip.com to have that child’s account terminated and information deleted. 

### In the Event of Merger or Sale:

In the event that ePaperFlip is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, or undergoes a change of control or any form of sale or transfer of some or all of its assets, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

### Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice:

our happ  
Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the ePaperFlip service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing revisions with respect to such information.

### Contacting ePaperFlip:

Please contact ePaperFlip with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: privacy@ePaperFlip.com
